I want to welcome to the Greater Allen Cathedral of New York, the one and only Amanda Seals.
We live in a world that has been set up to set us up.
We are only a very few generations removed from the civil rights movement, forgetting
that after the civil rights movement was the war on drugs, which has been swept under
the rug, but was an actual concerted, violent effort to prevent black people from enacting
their civil rights.
After the civil war, within two weeks, Lincoln was assassinated and everything that he had
tried to put forth that would begin a path forward for black folks to get some level of
economic equality was immediately reversed.
All them 40 acres and them mules, they said, give it back.
Thank you very much.